Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending,
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, is waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride the wave.
We're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun.
While our dreams are never ending.
Heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the world.
Just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
running forever Let's go along
with curiosity Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams and you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
This rock guy doesn't want
to let us go anywhere.
Like I told you, Fika
controls the entire palace.
We're lucky he hasn't crushed us yet.
Hey, Straw Hat.
You're sure your friend will
be okay? Zoro? Are you kidding?
He'll do great. Don't worry.
No matter what happens,
Zoro will pull through.
What's the trick here?
There has to be some place that can cut
this bastard that'll take him down for good.
That's not good!
We've got another executive!
He's a member of the Pika Army.
Gladius!
You can't beat him in your current form.
Rampo and I will draw his
attention and you run ahead!
That's the only way!
Don't you dare!
I won't have you sacrifice
yourselves on my behalf! Rampo!
We'll attack from both
sides at once! Roger!
No way!
Can't believe I'm stuck
exterminating these rats!
Let them go!
You think a toy can outrun me.
I ate the pop-pop fruit
and became a rupture man.
That means I can detonate my body
without causing harm to myself.
But that's not all.
I can also detonate anything inorganic.
Though a toy like you
won't survive the process.
Don't you dare.
I refuse to die.
Someone is counting on me!
Rebecca!
Looks like you're ready
to burst, little toy!
Jack, stop!
Who did that?
Soldier, have you seen my crew?
You saved me.
Freaky made it sound like he was with you.
There's no time.
You can talk later, Starhat.
So that's who it is.
Violet!
You little traitor.
You'll pay for turning your
back on the young master.
Oh, you want to fight?
What did I just say? Let go!
We have to run. Trust me. He's strong.
We'd be trapped here.
We have to end this.
Just head for the suit chamber.
Lady Viola, you're helping us now?
You recognize me? Of course!
Although I'm sure that
you've forgotten me.
That may be so.
But I've been watching you with my
clairvoyance for quite some time.
You and Rebecca as well. What?
I know it's been hard.
So thank you.
Get back here!
Your treachery won't
go unpunished, Violet.
You're dead!
I've never been on your side!
You give yourself too much credit.
For ten whole years, I've been
waiting for this opportunity!
I won't hear your
venomous words any longer.
Helmet, pop!
Lady Viola! Oh, no!
Sorry, I should've caught that.
Didn't get hurt too bad, did you?
Doesn't matter how we get there, right?
Where are you going?
The staircase is the other way!
This is bad.
What are you doing?
That should work.
Where did they go?
Young Master, why are you here?
Young Master?
The Doflamingo family
calls him young master.
That would be me.
There are some intruders in the palace.
You might want to wait upstairs
until we take care of them.
Upstairs?
I shall do no such thing.
You may do as you wish with the
intruders, but I'm heading underground.
I have business with Kanjido.
The samurai who disappeared
from the junkyard?
Huh?
Did you say he went missing?
Well, that certainly was
effective, wasn't it?
It's not time yet.
You have to wait first.
We have to hurry, and now we have to wait.
Mingo is right. There!
Just calm down.
The Tontara still need time to finish.
I thought your only objective
was to destroy the Smile Factory.
So what about Straw Hat?
His crew is teaming up
with the little people
from Green Bit—would
you mind telling me why?
Even for them, that
seems a bit capricious.
Doesn't it?
Little people—while you're at it—tell me
how they snuck into the underground port.
But why did
they decide to target Sugar?
I can't figure out their motivations
or how they arrived at this plan.
But they're doing a good job of
pissing me off at this point.
It's looking like... it's looking like
more than a simple coincidence.
That's not good.
Because that would mean they know
about this kingdom's dark secrets.
Don't just sit there!
The young master's speaking to you, Law!
Don't do it if it's gonna make you cry!
I swear, you two never change!
I already told you.
I don't have anything
to do with them anymore.
Our alliance ended.
Whatever they're doing out
there, it's none of my business.
A pity Violet isn't here.
She could see right through
you if you were lying.
By the way, you wouldn't happen to know
anything about this, would you, King Rick?
The Tontada were rather
fond of you, if I recall.
Father?
Why is he here?
Traffy's okay. That's good.
King Rick, after all these
years, you're still alive.
Your name is Kiros, huh?
Why don't you come with me, friend?
I will save you.
I swear it.
Let's go kick Mingo's ass already.
We still have to wait for the Tontara.
Did something happen to Leo?
Our window for victory is narrow,
but as long as he can restore
the toys to their human form,
I'll have my chance to strike
down Doflamingo once and for all.
My friends put their lives
on the line to protect me.
I will not fail, no matter the cost.
I'm counting on you, Leo.
Usoland!
Just give yourself up, Franky,
or we'll fire until you're dead!
You kidding me?
Why don't you shut the hell up?
Listen up, losers.
I'm going to go nuts and
wreck this place all day long.
Don't ask me why. What?
If I go underground with
these chumps chasing me,
It's just gonna make
things worse for the little
people I'm leaving operation
SOP in your hands, bros.
Give me everything you got.
Do your thing!
Who's a wind?
I got your back!
Whoa, what the hell's going on over there?
They said we've got intruders
We've also got master trebles and
no big deal those poor bastards
once you get on his bad side,
then you're as good as dead
What'd you guys take down already?
Jeez, you wanna die?
I dropped my guard.
I've been turned into a toy.
That means everyone
has forgotten about me.
Who's up?
Where did you go?
There's nothing I can do anymore.
It's all up to you now.
Whatever it takes, you
have to fight a way.
It's funny.
Why were they trying so hard
to make me eat this grape?
Probably poison, huh?
It certainly smells terrible.
I can't do it.
I can't fight anymore.
And don't worry.
If anything goes wrong, I'll
jump in and take over, okay?
Usoland.
Move! What happened? Come back!
I'm sorry, but I want to live. Who's up?
Where did you go?
We need you. Oh, hey.
How about I write a book to tell
future generations how brave you are?
The Honest Tantadas.
I've got a name already.
Good thing I'm alive, huh?
All of this is Frankie's fault anyway.
Why didn't he come here to help?
I won't let myself get killed just because
you guys think I'm some legendary hero.
Okay, I got away from the bad guys.
But I still need to find a
way out of this stupid place.
Probably can't worm my way through the
tunnel without them carrying me, huh?
Oh, wait.
They said that there
was a lift, didn't they?
Hey, hey, can everybody hear me?
Is it a show?
I hope you're not just standing there.
You didn't stop working, did you?
Ah, crap.
Get back to work.
Move those boxes.
What are you doing, stupid?
Hurry up, or else!
Someone's standing up to
the Don Quixote family!
I've been a toy for eight years and
I haven't seen this happen once!
Whoever you are, good luck!
Burn it all down!
Standing around?
I'm getting the hell out of this place!
What should we do with all of them?
Hmm... Huh?
Sugar?
Hey, are they saying something?
Sounds like it's... Huh? Huh?
U...
So...
Lund.
U...
So...
Uso... Lund.
Uso...
Lund, please.
Oh, come on, lift!
Where did they hide you?!
Uso...
Lund, please.
Lund...
Usuland?
Who's Usuland?
They said that name before, didn't they?
Usuland!
What's an Usuland?
I'm trying to run away!
Could you stop that?
What's going on here?
Who the heck is Usuland?
Oh, come on.
It's a friend of the Tontada, remember?
Moron, just die.
Only if you die first!
He won't lose to you!
Usuland is our hero!
Oh, you're a hero.
So, he's gonna come and
rescue you any second now.
He sure will.
We weren't quite strong enough.
But that's all right.
He'll fix everything.
He'll save this kingdom.
He'll rescue the toys who were forced to
slave away day after day at this port.
He's talking about us.
And he'll reunite us with our friends
who are held captive at the factory.
He'll restore all the toys we're
forced to put on a happy face.
He'll dry the tears and vanquish the
darkness they have buried in their hearts.
And the poor big people
who don't even know what
they've lost Will be reunited
with their loved ones.
And he'll save us too.
That's why I'm not afraid!
Cause we have a real hero on our side.
I don't need to be a hero!
No, thank you!
I almost feel sorry for you guys.
Your big hero lied to you. What?
Too bad.
Looks like you saps got fooled again.
You really think so?
Even though you're all beat up, this
Usulang guy still isn't coming to save you.
That says it all, doesn't it?
You think a real hero
would leave you like this?
Huh, do you?
But he told us he'd help
us if things got bad,
but he's not helping—I bet he's awesome!
We're laughing at you right now.
I bet there's some coward
out there who told you he'd
make everything right
somehow—whoever the heck he is,
but I also bet he'd shake it
out as soon as things look bad,
so you might as well give up hope.
Sorry, but he's right if you
want some advice—do like.
advice do like Goosalantin,
get the hell out of here!
It can't be!
Shut up!
He'll show you!
Goosalantin will save us
because our hero doesn't lie!
Do you know what he said?
Believe it or not, I'm a
descendant of Noland. Awesome!
He knew about Noland.
So when he tells us he'll save
the day, then we believe him.
And that means you're going
to be sorry real soon.
That's right.
He'll be here! Yeah!
A hero would never lie to us because
a hero will always keep his words.
So you'd better stop insulting
Oozolent or you're really gonna pay.
What is it?
If you're gonna laugh, better do it now.
Once Oozolent gets here,
then you're gonna cry.
He said Piggya.
That's funny.
So that's what you say when
you die, huh? Piggya? Leo!
What Leo said was true.
Usuland is on his way.
He'll carry out Operation S .O .P.
and he'll save all the Tantana.
Piggya!
Go ahead.
Be as cruel as you like.
Piggya!
Let's go ahead and go!
Let's see this hero of yours!
Oh man, that's not pretty bad!
Stop it!
Enough already! I'm here!
It's Usalad!
Usalad is here!
Gustav, you can do it!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why do you all trust me so
much, you little idiots?
You deserve to be crushed! What?
Treble was right.
Everything I told you was a lie! What?
In the first place, my name's not Usuland.
And I'm not a legendary hero, okay?
What?
I'm from the Straw Hat crew.
And my name is Usopp,
the Invincible Sniper!
I'm a pirate!
He's from the Straw Hats?
What are they doing here?
You're wrong!
Why would you say something like that?
Even if you're a pirate,
you still can be a hero!
A pirate's a pirate, okay?
Not a hero!
I already told you I
was lying! Give it up!
Don't make me repeat myself!
Stop having so much faith in me!
It's pointless!
Whoa, that's funny!
You came all the way back
here just to say that,
to let him know that you took them back!
That's right!
Otherwise, those fools would
wait around for me till they die!
If that happened, I wouldn't
be able to sleep at night.
So I wanted to thank them for
believing in a guy like me.
If I have to sacrifice
myself for them, that's fine.
It's much cooler than running away!
I'm Usopp—you hear me, you better!
Remember my name: Totanas.
If I die here fighting for you, you gotta
build a statue of me next to Nolan's.
You ask for a hero?
Well, sit back and watch
because I'm about to.
to You can't become one right now!
Usopp, I...
Usopp?
From the Straw Hats?
You think he's actually gonna save us?
After all this time?
Just give up.
I'll take my chances, special attack!
Green Star!
Plant on us! Yuck!
Yuck!
Yuck! Xunikin!
Yuck! Yuck!
Yuck!
How do you like that?
Now that's how a legendary hero does it!
Let's hear it for the
Sniper of the Straw Hats!
Captain Usopp!
Usopp! Usopp!
Our hero!
No, Usa!
Usa-land, our hero!
Look, it's Usa, you little bastards!
The legendary hero, Usa-land!
There was a report that you
were on the first floor, sir.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Maybe it was someone who looks like you.
Who the hell looks like me?
Something's going on. King Rick.
This is a fine sword.
If I turn back into a human,
this will do, Straw Hat!
My father was fighting
in the Coliseum today.
The old king he was spurred into action
after Doflamingo lied about his abdication.
Today I decided to fight back like him,
King Rick was fighting in the Coliseum.
There was a squabble in the slums.
Two people are dead.
The murderer is a teenage boy.
We have him surrounded.
King Rick!
My lord, wait!
He's far too dangerous! Stay away!
Hey!
He might look like some young punk,
but he's known throughout the
whole kingdom for his strength.
The king is in danger! Open fire!
No, don't shoot.
Put your guns down.
Huh?
But, my lord...
I heard you were in a terrible fight,
that you were all on your own
against dozens of angry thugs.
And in the end, more than half
of them were badly injured.
and two were killed that's true but
they ganged up on my best friend and
murdered him i was only taking revenge
for his death what are you a beast call me
whatever you like you haven't lived
my life you don't know a damn thing my
friend he was like a brother to me all
right he was the only person i ever trusted
Kiros was your name Come with me, please
The 15-year-old murderer Kiros is facing
off with one of our seasoned veterans
This coliseum is a sacred place
That's true skill If his blade wasn't
blunt, he would have killed that man
I'd call it savagery,
but here, it's skill.
How is Kiros doing?
He nearly killed all the convict
gladiators he was held with.
King Rick!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
King Rick is willing to release you on
parole if you're able to win 100 matches.
Even if it takes years, that's
how you may earn your freedom.
Yeah!
We won the consecutive victories!
Even our strongest gladiators
fell before the might of Kiros!
He's not in the league, but he's
won his freedom in no time at all!
That killer doesn't deserve to be free!
You're going to stay here.
I can't go where I'm not wanted.
Hmm. That's strange.
You care about other people's
opinion all of a sudden?
Shut up!
I should have known, people only like
beasts, as long as they stay in a cage.
200 victories!
Everybody take that guy out!
They can pay!
300 victories!
The heroes line up one after another,
but heroes cut them down to size!
Unbelievable!
We are witnessing an
unprecedented 1 ,000 victories!
Go, Kiros!
Nice work! You're awesome!
Hear it again, Kiros. Listen. Go away!
Don't you understand?
No matter where I go, for the
rest of my life, I'll be a beast.
A murderer!
I wish this world would forget about me!